Davis, Jackson; Papers apap141
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Jackson Davis Papers
1952-1997
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap141
9.83 cubic ft.
The papers of Jackson Davis document his environmental activism and work with environmental organizations.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department Special Collections and Archives, by Jackson Davis in September 2002, October 2004, and November 2004.
Biographical Sketch
Jackson Davis is a native of New York's Capital Region who has been involved with a large number of environmental organizations and enviromental programs at the local and regional level for more than three decades. Davis earned a BA in Science Education in 1964 and an M.L.S. in 1970 from the State University of New York at Albany, as the University at Albany, SUNY was then known. After graduating, Jackson Davis worked as a bibliographer at such organizations as the National Science Foundation Institute for Science Teachers and the State University of New York at Albany Atmospheric Sciences Research Center. In September 1971 he became an administrator at the Albany County Environmental Advisory Council, which had recently joined with the councils of three other counties to form the Four County Recycling Committee. Davis' work there was research on such topics as solid waste recycling and the creation and protection of open space areas including the Albany Pine Bush. Additional Information about Davis' employment history is available in Series 8.
During the early 1970s, Jackson Davis participated in the Environmental Forum program at the State University of New York at Albany. This was a public forum that brought local speakers on environmental topics to campus for lectures and a class in the Environmental Studies program. The program began in 1970 and lasted until it was eliminated by budget cuts in 1977.
Jackson Davis has also been involved in the Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council. Formed in 1972, this council was responsible for preparing reports and providing advice for the town council. Davis was chair of the advisory council during a controversial proposal to build the Brainard Quarry at Snake Mountain during the mid-1990s. Other organizations represented in the collection include the Futures Group of Glastonbury, Connecticut, for which Davis was a research assistant from 1975-1977, and the New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance, which promoted sustainable local methods of food production. Other groups that Jackson Davis has worked with, but are not represented in the collection, include the Capital District Regional Planning Commission, the US Coast Guard's Hazardous Waste Amelioration Project, and the Nature Conservancy.
Scope and Contents
The papers of Jackson Davis document his environmental activism and work with environmental organizations. The collection consists of publications, minutes, notes, news clippings, and memoranda from local and regional environmental groups Davis has worked with, as well as a collection of subject files created by Davis relating to a wide variety of environmental topics. Also included are a collection of Davis' bibliographical projects and a number of environmental health publications collected by Davis' father, Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr. Dr. Davis served as health commissioner in Rensselaer County and is represented in this collection by some of his collected publications.
Jackson Davis worked for a number of organizations doing bibliographical research. Much of the material in the collection was created through the collection of sources and compiling of bibliographies. Part of Davis' research process was the listing of subject headings, in general or in Library of Congress format. The Bibliography series contains research on certain environmental topics that have no direct relation to the organizations that Davis worked for. Research materials produced for a specific organization are retained in the appropriate series. There is little biographical information in this collection; instead it's strength is the papers produced and collected by Jackson Davis and the various environmental organizations.
Several collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives provide further information on the environmental issues that were of concern to Davis. For a complete list of related collections, see the Conservation and the Environment subject guide. Of particular note are the papers of Robert Reinow (UA-902.009) and Lou Ismay, both of whom were involved in the Environmental Forum while teaching at the State University of New York at Albany.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr., 1952, 1954, 1957-1970, Undated
Series 2 - Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council, 1967-1997
Series 3 - Albany County Environmental Management Council and Four County Committee on Recycling, 1962, 1965-1966, 1968-1973
Series 4 - Futures Group, 1966-1976
Series 5 - New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance, 1970-1971, 1973-1979, Undated
Series 6 - Environmental Forum, 1967-1974
Series 7 - Bibliographies, 1965-1985, Undated
Series 8 - Subject Files, 1956-1997, Undated
Series 9 - News Clippings, 1968-1996, Undated
All series are arranged alphabetically, with the exception of Series 9 which is arranged chronologically.
Rensselaer County, New York; Conservation and the Environment; Environmentalism--New York (State); Hazardous wastes--New York (State); Environmental education--New York (State); Conservation of natural resources--New York (State)--Citizen participation.; Environmental policy--Social aspects.; Quarries and quarrying--New York (State); Albany Pine Bush Preserve (Albany, N.Y.); Correspondence; Clippings; Publications; Newsletters; Reports; Periodicals; Minutes; Notes; Maps; Bibliographies; Davis, Jackson.; Davis, H. Jackson.; Ismay, Louis F.; Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council.; Albany County Environmental Management Council.; Futures Group.--Connecticut--Glastonbury.; New York (State).--Dept. of Environmental Conservation.; New York State Coalition for Local Self Reliance.; State University of New York.--Atmospheric Sciences Research Center.
- Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr., 1952; 1954; 1957-1970; Undated; 1; 0.5 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  Papers in this series relate to the professional career of Jackson Davis' father, Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr., who served as public health commissioner for Rensselaer County. His files contain mostly collected publications. The most significant of these is Water Resources in Rensselaer County, authored by Davis Sr. Other publications in the series were produced by a variety of organizations, including the New York State Department of Health, the National Tuberculosis Association, and the National Health Forum. There are also a few subject files on medical and environmental topics, including polio, the aging process, conservation, and air quality.
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, "Intergovernmental Responsibility for Waste Supply and Sewage Disposal...", 1962 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 1)
  - Aging Process, True Magazine, Article, 1963 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 2)
  - Air Pollution and Air Quality, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 3)
  - "Are You Concerned About Water? You Will Be," Geological Survey Circular 425, 1960 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 4)
  - Association for Voluntary Sterilization, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 5)
  - Conservation, 1958; Undated (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, in Spanish, 1963 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 7)
  - Federated Garden Clubs of New York State, 1966 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 8)
  - Hilleboe, Dr. Herman E., Honorary Dinner, Programs, 1963 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 9)
  - Hospital Blood Assignment and Transfusion Service, Computerized Data Processing, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 10)
  - Medical Tribune, February 22, 1963 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 11)
  - National Health Forum, Urban Sprawl and Health, Report, 1958 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 12)
  - National Tuberculosis Association, Brochures, 1962; 1964-65 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 13)
  - New York State Department of Health, "Act Now for Clear Air", Undated (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 14)
  - New York State Department of Health, "Cattaragus Creek Drainage Basin," Lake Erie-Niagara River Drainage Basin Series Report #4, 1957 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 15)
  - New York State Department of Health, "Private and Pump-Out Facilities Expected to Be in Operation by March 1, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 16)
  - New York State Department of Health, "The Pure Waters Program and You, 1969 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 17)
  - New York State Department of Health, "Pure Waters Progress", 1969 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 18)
  - New York State Department of Health, "What You Should Know About New York's Waters", Undated (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 19)
  - New York State Forest Land Use Conference, 1963 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 20)
  - Outdoor Advertising, Articles, 1958 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 21)
  - Pennsylvania, Conservation Issues, 1954; 1957-1958 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 22)
  - Playboy Magazine, "The Public Be Dammed", 1969 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 23)
  - Phosphate Detergents, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 24)
  - Polio, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 25)
  - Rensselaer County Health Department, Map of Towns, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 26)
  - Rensselaer County Regional Water Resources, Suggested Policy Statement, 1958 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 27)
  - Rensselaer County Soil Conservation District, "Soils and the Soil Survey: What They Mean to You in Rensselaer County", Undated (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 28)
  - State of New York Conservation Department, "Two Year Progress Report on Land Acquisition for Parks and Recreation", 1963 (Box 1 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 29)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, 1952; 1962-1965; Undated (Box 2 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 1)
  - Water Pollution, Sample Speech, Undated (Box 2 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 2)
  - Water Resources in Rensselaer County, 1961 (Box 2 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 3)
  - Water Resources in Rensselaer County, 1961 (Box 2 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 4)
  - The Wilderness Society, The Living Wilderness, Spring, 1962 (Box 2 (1-Dr. H. Jackson Davis, Sr.), Folder 5)
- Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council, 1967-1997; 2; 2.50 cubic ft.
  This series contains items related to the Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council, such as minutes, correspondence, press releases, and reports. Included are materials from the New York Department of Environmental Conservation (DEC) received by Jackson Davis as chair of the council. Major sections include materials generated by the creation of a Natural Resources Inventory for Nassau and items related to the proposed creation of Brainard Quarry by Lane Construction. For a general overview of the latter controversy, see folder titled, "Brainard Quarry, Timeline, 1992-1997."
  - Brainard Quarry, Application Index, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 1)
  - Brainard Quarry, Articles on Mining, 1987; 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 2)
  - Brainard Quarry, Citizens Against Lane Mining (CALM), 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 3)
  - Brainard Quarry, Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 4)
  - Brainard Quarry, Draft Environmental Impact Statements, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 5)
  - Brainard Quarry, Draft Environmental Impact Statements, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 6)
  - Brainard Quarry, Draft Environmental Impact Statements, Review and Comment, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 7)
  - Brainard Quarry, Freedom of Information Request, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 8)
  - Brainard Quarry, Handwritten Notes, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 9)
  - Brainard Quarry, Index of Department of Environmental Conservation Files, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 10)
  - Brainard Quarry, Lane Construction Permit Application, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 11)
  - Brainard Quarry, Nassau CAC Public Statement, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 12)
  - Brainard Quarry, Nassau Union of Concerned Citizens, Correspondence with Town of Nassau, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 13)
  - Brainard Quarry, Nassau Union of Concerned Citizens, Fliers, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 14)
  - Brainard Quarry, Nassau Union of Concerned Citizens, Press Releases, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 15)
  - Brainard Quarry, Notes from Public Hearing, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 16)
  - Brainard Quarry, Permit Hearing Materials, 1989-1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 17)
  - Brainard Quarry, Revisions to the State Environmental Quality (SEQR) Act, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 18)
  - Brainard Quarry, Scoping Checklist, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 19)
  - Brainard Quarry, Tax Maps and Assessments, Undated (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 20)
  - Brainard Quarry, Timeline, 1992-1997 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 21)
  - Brainard Quarry, Town Board and Planning Board Minutes, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 22)
  - Brainard Quarry, Town Clerk's File, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 23)
  - Brainard Quarry, Zoning, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 24)
  - Burden Lake Country Club Expansion, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 25)
  - Capital District Regional Planning Commission, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 26)
  - "Conservation Commissions in New York," New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1988 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 28)
  - "Critical Areas: A Handbook for Local Government", 1981 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 29)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Annual Reports, 1984; 1987; 1995-1996 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 30)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Division of Solid Waste, 1986-1988 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 31)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Division of Solid Waste, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 32)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Division of Solid Waste, Recycling, 1982; 1986 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 33)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Division of Solid Waste, Recycling, 1988-1990; 1993 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 34)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Division of Water, 1985; 1989 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 35)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Division of Water, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 36)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Hazardous Waste, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 1)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Hazardous Waste, 1984; 1987-1988; 1993 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 2)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Hazardous Waste Site Remediation, 1986-1991 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 3)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Hazardous Waste Site Remediation, 1992; 1994-1995; 1997 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 4)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Household Hazardous Waste, 1986; 1990-1991 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 5)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Information Packets, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 6)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Information Packets, 1988-1990 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 7)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, "Let's Clear The Air" Program, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 8)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Miscellaneous Publications, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 9)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, "Return a Gift to Wildlife" Program, Undated (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 10)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Solid Waste Management Plan, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 11)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Water Week Materials, 1989-1994 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 12)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation Publications, Wetlands, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 13)
  - "Directory of Publications, Environmental Management Councils in New York State," New York State Association of Environmental Management Councils, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 14)
  - Flood Insurance Rate Maps, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 15)
  - "Flood Insurance Study," FEMA, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 16)
  - Hard Rock Industries Mining Permit Application, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 17)
  - Hudson River Authority Act, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 18)
  - "Land Use Analysis for the Town and Village of Nassau", 1967 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 19)
  - "Land Use Regulations, Town of Nassau," Nassau Land Use Commission, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 20)
  - Local Government Implementation of the Freshwater Wetlands Act, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 21)
  - Mining Network, Undated (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 22)
  - "Municipal Advisory Councils for Environmental Conservation," New York State Office for Local Government, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 23)
  - Nassau Conservation Advisory Council, Minutes, 1968-1996 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 24)
  - Nassau Conservation Advisory Council, Resolution Creating CAC, By-laws, Legislation, Member List, 1972; 1982; 1996 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 25)
  - Nassau Lake Survey, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 26)
  - Nassau Master Plan Committee, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 27)
  - Nassau Quarry, 1982 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 28)
  - "Natural Resources Inventory, A Guide to the Process," New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1975 (Box 2 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 29)
  - Natural Resources Inventory, Census Data, 1991 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 1)
  - Natural Resources Inventory, Geologic Inventory Notes, Undated (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 2)
  - Natural Resources Inventory, Instructional, Undated (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 3)
  - Natural Resources Inventory, Miscellaneous Material, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 4)
  - Natural Resources Inventory, Notes, 1974 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 5)
  - Natural Resources Inventory, Open Spaces Inventory, Instructional, 1974 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 6)
  - Natural Resources Inventory, Soil Mapping, 1971-1974 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 7)
  - New York State Conference on the Environment, 1989 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 8)
  - "The Official Rensselaer County Building Permit Report," Rensselaer County Planning Office, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 9)
  - "Population Growth and Development in the Capital District Region," Capital District Regional Planning Commission, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 10)
  - "Regional Wetlands Concepts Plan, Emergency Wetlands Resources Act," US Fish and Wildlife Service, 1990 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 11)
  - "Rensselaer County Data Book," Rensselaer County Planning Board, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 12)
  - "Rensselaer County Master Plan", circa 1988 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 1)
  - "Rensselaer County Land Use," Rensselaer County Planning Board, 1968 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 2)
  - "Rensselaer County Natural Resources Inventory Handbook," Rensselaer County Environmental Management Council, 1980 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 3)
  - Sewage Treatment, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 4)
  - "The State of the Environment," The Rensselaer County Environmental Management Council, 1974 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 5)
  - Town of Nassau Land Use and Development Regulation, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 6)
  - Town of Nassau Land Use Law, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 7)
  - Town of Nassau Special Board Meeting, August 6, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 8)
  - Town of Nassau Unsafe Buildings Law, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Town of Nassau Conservation Advisory Council), Folder 9)